[
    {
        "title" : "Words"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "She studied sculpture at Saint Martin’s College",
      "answer": "Common People – Pulp"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Lonely rivers flow to the sea, to the sea",
        "answer": "Unchained Melody – Various artists eg The Righteous Brothers, Robson and Jerome, Gareth Gates etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "When the night has come, and the land is dark",
        "answer": "Stand By Me – Ben E King"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "You shake my nerves and you rattle my brain, too much love drives a man insane",
        "answer": "Great Balls of Fire – Jerry Lee Lewis"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "But February made me shiver, with every paper I’d deliver",
        "answer": "American Pie – Don McLean"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Baby ‘cause in the dark you can’t see shiny cars and that’s when you need me there, with you I’ll always share",
        "answer": "Umbrella – Rihanna"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "You call me up again just to break me like a promise, so casually cruel in the name of being honest",
        "answer": "All Too Well – Taylor Swift"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "I come home in the morning light, my mother says when you gonna live your life right",
        "answer": "Girls Just Want to Have Fun – Cyndi Lauper"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Young teacher, the subject of schoolgirl fantasy",
        "answer": "Don’t Stand So Close to Me – The Police"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I work all night, I work all day to pay the bills I have to pay, ain’t it sad",
        "answer": "Money, Money, Money – Abba"
    }
]
